unitrust-direct.com 2011-10-28

# Unitrust Direct Asset Management & Advisory :: Where experience meets innovation

|  | 

## Announcements  
  
---  
  
  * Fri, 07 Oct 2011  

### PDF Brochure

The official Unitrust Direct PDF brochure is now available for download. Containing the full information on company`s background, mission and commitments, as well as a complete list of investment products, the official PDF Brochure is virtually all you need to know about Unitrust Direct. 

 3 comment(s) All news 

## Testimonials  
  
---  
  
" Great and trustworthy online investment program. Always paying instantly and without problems. " 

**HYIP-Pulse.com Staff**  

## World markets  
  
---  
| 

Fri, 28 Oct 2011 02:48:33 (BST)  
  
---  
BSE Sensex | 

17,288.83

| 

+33.97  
  
CAC 40 | 

3,368.62

| 

+199.00  
  
FTSE 100 | 

5,713.82

| 

0.00  
  
Hang Seng Index | 

19,688.70

| 

0.00  
  
Nikkei 225 | 

9,061.55

| 

+135.01  
  
S&P TSX | 

12,465.44

| 

+279.38  
  
S&P/ASX 200 | 

4,386.20

| 

+38.00  
  
Shanghai | 

2,435.61

| 

0.00  
  
TSEC | 

7,565.21

| 

0.00  
  
## Currencies  
  
---  
| 

Fri, 28 Oct 2011 02:48:33 (BST)  
  
---  
AUD/USD | 

1.0711 

| 

+0.0301  
  
GBP/USD | 

1.6086 

| 

+0.0115  
  
USD/CAD | 

0.9917 

| 

-0.0122  
  
USD/CNY | 

6.3590 

| 

+0.0056  
  
USD/HKD | 

7.7671 

| 

-0.0061  
  
USD/JPY | 

75.9700 

| 

-0.2000  

## Online Privacy Statement

Unitrust Direct Co. is concerned about your right to privacy. When you submit an account application form or other forms or request information on our products, you give us information such as your name, address etc. Information, provided by you is used to help us process your registration, fulfil your request or respond to your inquiry. We do not disclose non-public personal information about our potential, current and former customers unless allowed or required by law. 

### Information we may collect and use

When you visit our website, the following non-personal data is collected:

  * The type of browser used
  * Geographical region the connection is originating from
  * Date and time of the connection
  * Pages visited during the connection
  * Date and time of the connection

This information is used solely to determine traffic patterns on the site.

### Security of Information

All of your personal information is stored in a secure encrypted database. Access to this database is limited to authorized persons. Our employees are authorized to access your information only when they need it to provide you with products and services or to maintain your accounts. Employees who have access to your personal information are required to keep it strictly confidential. We provide training to our employees about the importance of protecting the privacy of your information.

### Miscellaneous

Unitrust Direct may change the Privacy Notice in our sole discretion without notice or liability to you.

Last revised: May 23, 2011  
  
---  
  
[](https://unitrust-direct.com/) Copyright (c) 2005-2011 Unitrust Direct Asset Management & Advisory. All rights reserved.
